hello welcome
it was requested that i'd do a video
in my bar so here we are doing a video
in the bar it's going to be a review
video of this helmet it's a pretty cool
helmet it's the schubert c3 pro you know
now if you're here for a professional
review by somebody who's getting paid to
say all this or somebody that has any
idea what they're talking about
that that's probably not me
but if you would like an honest review
of somebody who bought this helmet and
uses this helmet
and bought it because
they were on a budget and turn out this
helmet is amazing and we're just gonna
like talk about it i love this helmet
then you've come to the right place
now look this helmet has features okay i
don't know them all
[Music]
but i do know it's very lightweight very
comfortable it seals off your entire
neck head area
it's very cushy gives you hugs
everywhere it is a modular helmet
it's very aerodynamic blocks out a lot
of wind noise it's got an internal visor
i like to use that it's got some really
cool venting
i'm sorry i didn't memorize all the the
stuff about it you know we're going to
put that over here for you to read
because memorizing that stuff is for
people who get like thousands of likes
and get paid
to do this
so
hope you got all your packs we are going
to take this thing on the road or we did
yesterday i'm not doing it now i did
that portion of it
yesterday but why don't we have a nice
overview of the helmet huh
we'll show you the things
stuff about it i talk about price
yesterday in a little bit when we take
it for a spin
got a really good deal on it it's a
really nice helmet i love this helmet
my favorite helmet i've ever had
so
[Music]
um without further ado let's yesterday
take this bad boy on the road huh
[Music]
hey look we're on the motorcycle wearing
that helmet that guy was talking about
yeah the schubert c3 pro pretty cool
just a quick rip around the airport
today i live like right outside the
cincinnati airport
and if i just want to go for a quick
cruise you know i'll go around it it's
got a couple different routes and i'll
just travel around it you know go look
at some aeroplanes at the uh
viewing area beautiful weather we're
having yes
61 degrees and
clear and sunny so right now we're about
60 miles per hour and this helmet does a
great job of diverting the wind i love
it any other helmet i've ever had
granted i do have a fairing now
but i've also ridden this bike with
four
four or five different helmets and this
is
this is amazing i love it i love this
helmet i've been riding with it for
about a month now i think i could say
whether it does a good job or not and
you know it does a pretty good job my
head is not all shaking around
everywhere but we are gonna hit the
interstate for just a minute uh to cross
the border to mexico i'll show you guys
how how well it keeps the noise down
uh the
shaking
beating your head all over the place you
really don't get that with this helmet
it has great aerodynamics which having
the camera and the ricardo kind of
cancels a little bit of that out but
still
even with all that i think it does a
mighty fine job that's the end of one of
the runways right there and also this
mic does a great job of cutting out the
wind noise even if it was a very windy
helmet you would still get
quite a lot and it's it's pretty
windy right now because it's
you know
icky and it looks great i love the look
of this helmet i don't know what all the
guy down at the bar said
he didn't do that until tomorrow he
probably gave you some stats of you know
like what it weighs and different color
options or something i'm not sure i i
can't tell you any of that right now but
it's
my goodness it's very light so i just
wanted to do a quick rip because i did
just get off and it's going to be
getting dark soon and it's kind of
chilly out it's kind of icky looking out
but i still wanted to get out for a
minute and talk to you guys because i
love y'all and my bike's pretty loud i
feel like on the last couple videos that
i had this helmet on
you didn't hear it too much i mean you
heard it but it's not
overbearing
that guy thinks i want to race oh man
i'm just i'm just being loud you ain't
got to take off go get yourself arrested
you want to race crossing over to mexico
here in just a minute i'll give you a
race old boy
[Music]
when you're just chilling you have it
like this it clicks in pretty well it
stays
even at high speeds it'll just stay like
this pretty nice but it's kind of chilly
today and that's what another thing i
love about this helmet is it doesn't
have a chin curtain it's just got a full
like
the whole thing is hugging you
and that takes a minute to get used to
because i hate when things touch my neck
hate it
and i thought it would be an issue but
after the the first two or three rides
on this thing
it ain't a thing i mean if i think about
it it's still there but yeah
border patrol don't get me
we're just gonna do a real quick one on
the interstate
i think that's good enough huh got my
pants flying up i really don't feel like
i need to yell to
get my voice to come through you get a
little bit of vibration but my old
helmet man when i hit these speeds here
i couldn't see at all i had to slow down
i couldn't read street signs i couldn't
just give me a headache
i could see perfectly i have a little
bit of shaking not bad at all
i mean when you're going
over the speed limit
that's gonna happen but i can move my
head any direction it's not whipping me
around
it's not bothering me i consider these
speeds all day which i've slowed down
now but still they're going faster than
me unacceptable so i mean the bike's
pretty loud
i got some wind noise but i still don't
feel like i need to yell you know i've
got plenty of room to talk and
roll my eyes around in here
it's a really great lightweight modular
helmet i'll say that this is my exit
we're going to give it
one more
one more of these guys
but you know they're gonna block us in
put my pant leg down it's blowing up now
i look like a dork
with my white socks hanging out
hey what do you think of my helmet
let's give her one of these huh
so i will say the the few reviews i
watched on this helmet those guys did a
really great job
but uh i don't think any of them lived
in a place where they could easily
access the interstate one was like a guy
on an adventure or a dual sport
and
the other one was in like italy
like
in some small italian town it's pretty
neat so i didn't see any of them hitting
the interstate and like high wind noise
that one guy got up to like 60 or 65 or
something
and i will say also on a chilly day like
this when i'm
breathing a little harder because it's a
little chilly the pin lock the pin lock
is a must i didn't touch on the
ventilation while i was up on going fast
that's the only negative thing
i have so far and the other videos those
guys will agree
it's not the greatest ventilation
it's got good vent venting i will give
it that i mean you feel it when you open
it you do feel it
uh the top has different settings
i think let's see yeah
it's got like a higher and a lower
more open more closed type deal
the bottom one is just one little flap
without the visor you feel it a lot
better
but i like to wear the visor down and
you'll feel a little bit
and even then it's just a gentle breeze
which is
i haven't had an issue with it here's
the airport
i was going to stop right here you could
see
at the other end of this stop light
there's a viewing area and you can go
watch the planes take off and land
but
i'm tired and i would like to be home
when i stop at the stop signs i like to
you know i like to pull the visor up a
bit and breathe and then of course it's
modular so you can flip up the top
which that guy down at the bar probably
explained to you
uh tomorrow i can't do it right now
because i'm i got my mic plugged in
don't want to yank my mic out but in
case you want to look super duper cool
you can always lift the front up and
impress all your friends now i did
mention
that this mic does an amazing job of uh
blocking out background noise and wind
noise and it
it picks you up really well over the
loud night
that's going to be a different video i
want to do a video of like
i have finally
gotten good motovlogging audio i had it
once
it was kind of a pain in the ass i used
the the separate recorder i had a
different helmet
and then i went to
the the media mod
with a different mic
and that still worked pretty well on
that original helmet
and then i switched to my hjc i90 at
honey i'll tell you
all sound quality went straight out the
door here's a clip of that
i love my coffee rides and i love my new
insta360 camera so i uh ditched the mic
i was using which was a turtle beach
headset mic it was okay it got me
started it was like 20 bucks
um
the biggest complaint i have about it is
it only recorded one channel
so when i'm editing i'd have to extract
the audio and turn it into a
stereo file
you know
where it plays both sides
this one
records both channels and it's very
small
it's tiny you wouldn't think it has that
kind of power but i've never heard it
pop or crack or anything no matter how
loud it gets
the only issue that i have and it's not
a mic or a helmet problem i think it's
the gopro problem because i record
through my gopro i don't know yet
i haven't solved it it's the popping in
between cuts when i cut my clips you get
a little
you get a little pop that's very
annoying some people say they don't
notice it
i notice a big time and i've tried
crossfading and that just kind of gives
this weird little static sound i'm
dealing with the pop for now and with
this helmet and this mic it has improved
and i like that but it's still there but
back to the helmet it's a really great
helmet aeroplanes
all of the aeroplanes
they just built the amazon hub it's like
the one of the main us
amazon hubs
right there and i live like right at the
end of it that's dhl amazon all that
what was i saying oh it's derby day and
here's the uh horse park the turf way
horse park they're remodeling they tore
it down and they're rebuilding but
they still have a track
i don't know if
they're doing anything right now but
it's derby day what was i saying again
oh
so this is of course the uh
the schubert c3 pro and they now have
the c5 and 5 pro which i've heard the c3
was really
um
really works well
for like cruising and fairing bikes
i'll agree because that's what i have
and i love the helmet
the four or the five
from what i've heard
i've not bought these helmets because i
cannot confirm it
and i really haven't looked into them
because i bought this one because you
know budget but i think that the four or
the five or maybe both i don't know
are more aimed at a sport touring
type of riding
or wind deflection or something
something of that nature
see here's the amazon hub
we're still building stuff up there
and when i say budget
i got a great deal on this thing i paid
314 dollars
and i'll put the website down here
because i don't remember it but it came
from the netherlands and it really only
took like a week week and a half to get
here not bad at all
but checking the prices on revzilla or
trying to get it domestically oh that's
a terrible crisis revzilla was up like
five six hundred bucks
i haven't saw it somewhere for 800 which
is like the original retail value of
this helmet
heck no i'm gonna put that website down
there who even are you that's probably
another spam person
i don't even know you
but i'll put the website that i got it
from down there 314 versus upwards of
800 that's insane that's what they
charge for these things when they're
brand new like
five years ago
anyway
is this helmet worth it
does this helmet still hold up to the
newer helmets i don't know i haven't had
the newer helmets
but i will say i love this helmet it's
so comfortable it hugs you everywhere
it's got great padding you can
shake your head all over the dang place
and it stays nice and tight
the ventilation as i mentioned not the
best it's a little warm
but it does good enough
it's cute enough for me
i don't suffocate so i'm gonna give this
thing like a
i'll give it like a four and a half just
because the ventilation i love the way
it looks
i love the way it feels i love the way
it fits
i love the weight
it's the lightest
full face or modular helmet that i've
ever had it's fantastic it's like three
point
something pounds the guy at the bar told
you
earlier that
we'll record that tomorrow
he's weird he doesn't it's
what you'll see he's
he's goofy or you saw i don't know saw
that he was goofy what a weirdo but i am
too close to my house now to show you
all where i live
so
that's the schubert
schubert super schuberth sherbert
c3 pro
modulor
and uh i will recommend this helmet
all day every day
okay that wasn't your turn but all right
you go ahead that's cool
if you're watching
your mom's a so thanks for riding
along and checking out the helmet and
looking how cool i look
and we'll see you next time huh i love
you guys subscribe if you like
like if you like
comment if you like
just do whatever you want you don't have
to do any of it probably not even still
here good helmet
love you guys
see you next time
[Music]
you